Let's get this party started.
Get Me Roger Stone is a documentary film directed by Daniel DiMauro.
From his days of testifying at the Watergate hearings to advising recent presidential candidate Donald Trump, Roger
Stone has long offended people on both sides of the political fence as a force in conservative America.
Outspoken author, pundit, ahead of his time
election strategist, this is his story.
Self, played by Roger Stone.
Self, played by Donald Trump.
Self, played by Paul Manafort.
Self, played by Jeffrey Toobin.
Self, played by Jane Mayer.
Self, played by Nydia Stone.
Get Me Roger Stone is a 2017 American documentary film written and
directed by Dylan Bank, Daniel DiMauro and Morgan Pehme.
The film explores the life and career of Republican political strategist and
lobbyist Roger Stone, a longtime advisor to Donald Trump.
The film was released on Netflix on May 12, 2017.